[English subtitles are available]
[Song Of The Moon]
[Episode 5]
Lu Sheng.
After I leave,
remember to pick some pears.
Practice magic more often.
Don't waste time.
Supreme God,
I will follow your instructions.
Lu Sheng.
[Immortal Palace, Four Seasons Monument]
You promised
to follow my instructions, didn't you?
How much longer do you want me to wait?
Who are you?
Tell me your name.
Demon King in White?
Why is he here?
Miss Liu Shao.
My name is Kho.
I belong to you.
You belong to me?
Kho?
What is he talking about...
You were in a hurry to chase the spider demon,
and dropped me out.
This demon looks good.
This guy is up to no good.
You mean
your master, Demon King in White, had a fight with someone
and got injured.
Then he left you alone
to run your own course?
I'm just a little fish demon.
My life doesn't matter.
A fish demon's life should also be respected.
This doesn't make sense.
That...
That Demon King in White is awful.
How could he even abandon his own clansman?
He doesn't deserve to be Head of the clan.
I also think this Demon King
is awful.
When he ran into powerful demons,
he would just turn around and run away.
But when it's our little Liu Shao,
he would snatch her treasure.
He is really
cowardly and despicable
without a little bit shame.
How could he promote himself
as a kind, generous,
and polite Demon King?
Bah!
He's just a scumbag.
A typical hypocrite.
Bah!
I thought I met
a good man who was righteous.
But it turns out that he's just a scumbag.
Scum!
Scumbag!
Damn fish demon.
You don't look well.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Maybe I've been away from water for too long.
Then that means
you've been dehydrated.
Fattie.
Leave it to me.
Demon King in White,
I'll teach you a lesson.
Since you know my identity,
why don't you leave now?
I don't fear you.
What's wrong with them?
They haven't met before, have they?
Wait.
I'll kill you.
Let's see what you can do to me.
You damn fish demon!
Has the fish become a demon?
It's originally a fish demon.
Kho, are you alright?
Kho!
Don't worry.
Even if something happens to us,
it can still stay unscathed.
You...
Did I wet your clothes?
I'm sorry.
I've indeed been away from water for too long.
I can't help it when I see water.
You're still alive?
That's great.
Brother,
We haven't caught a demon yet.
Let's get him back and hand him in.
You're so smart.
No.
This is my demon.
How can you hand it in? No way.
Look, my Miss
is the only one with beauty and kindness here.
Liu Shao.
He is...
This guy's still pretending...
Fine, you can continue.
I'll see how long you can keep pretending.
Because of this spider demon,
we really have to go back empty-handed.
We'll definitely get punished again...
[Imperial Cosmo Hall]
I think I know what happened now.
However,
you didn't get any prey.
And you indeed came back empty-handed.
I have to punish you.
Lord,
it was I that led the team this time.
I'm willing to get punished alone for them.
In that case,
I'll punish you
to clean the Pearl Pavilion for a month,
what do you think?
-Thank you, Lord. -Thank you, Lord.
Lu Li.
You promised to get the King Herb for me.
Don't forget it.
You may leave.
Call Du Mingchong here.
Yes.
[Bird Demon]
Chong.
Lu Li's team came back empty-handed.
What do you think?
He let you down.
He should be punished severely.
But I think
you disappointed me more.
I don't understand.
You don't understand?
[Wu]
On the 13th day of the first lunar month,
[Spider Demon]
Du Mingchong
hunted a spider demon at the East Mountain Pass.
Male.
Long hair.
200 years of demon power.
It was because of my carelessness
that the demon escaped.
Sorry for not reporting it in time.
Please forgive me, Lord.
Was it really a matter of your being careless?
Or maybe you did it on purpose?
[Bird demon, Spider Demon]
You know it clearly.
I really didn't notice it when it ran away.
I swear.
Please listen to me.
Forget it.
I don't mind it anymore.
You may leave.
Yes.
Don't let me down again.
I always hope
he can do the right thing,
be on the right path,
and become
the future Marquis Wuyang.
After all, he is the son of your old friend.
What a pity.
But
Lu Li...
Master.
Feng.
Why are you back?
I thought
you've been suffering a cough.
In the past,
my junior fellow was here looking after you.
Now,
he has gone to Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
I was afraid that you would be left alone,
so I brought some herbal medicines.
The Chuanbei herb-pear juice
was bought by him, right?
He's meddlesome.
I'm used to it.
How is Li?
Not bad.
He went through a lot with Liu Shao.
After all, Liu Shao is a spoiled young lady.
She's new to the Marquis' Mansion.
Li should help him from time to time.
With his guidance,
Liu Shao's cultivation has improved a lot.
Did he ever mention the Moon Sword?
Well,
maybe he's been too busy with helping Liu Shao,
and had no time to care about the Moon Sword.
You mean
he only cares about Liu Shao
and hasn't kept mind
on what I told him to do?
No, Master.
The Moon Sword is so important.
He will remember it.
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
Brother.
I'm ready.
For what?
We should share weal and woe together.
How can we let you be punished alone?
Such a good boy.
But think about it.
If you share the woe with me,
then Xue also has to suffer together with us.
She just recovered.
Don't you care about her?
Care about her?
No.
Wait, it seems that I care about her.
Besides, Liu Shao will go with me.
You two don't have to worry about it.
You're injured. I'm worried about you.
I'm worried about you too.
Tell me, do you think I look good?
Actually...
Actually,
you also think I look good,
right?
Master?
Master.
Why are you here?
I heard that you'd been busy lately.
So I came to see you.
Actually,
I'm fine.
The Demon King in White
sneaked into Marquis Wuyang's Mansion,
so I was thinking about
how to get the King Herb back
from him.
Was it for the King Herb,
or for Liu Shao?
Master.
We took so much money from her.
If she is in danger,
we have to protect her, don't we?
You kept no mind on the tasks I gave you, did you?
Instead, you care so much about this girl!
I remember you hated her.
You didn't even want to come with her.
Actually,
after getting along with her,
I found that
she's ctually
not that spoiled.
She's hardworking,
and sincere.
Master,
she's not good-for-nothing.
Have you gotten enamoured with her?
No.
How could it be?
Master
doesn't want me to be with her?
You can't be together.
Why?
Master, you don't like her?
So you asked me to approach her
just because she can help me draw the Moon Sword?
It doesn't matter if I like her or not.
You should know her spirit fire
is incompatible with yours.
You know it.
I don't need to explain.
You can only get each other restrained
and impaired.
Your fate is also in opposition.
You're destined to get each other impaired.
Your love for each other
can only get both of you harmed.
You wanted to know where you were from,
and that was why I asked you to enter Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
It was for making you draw the Moon Sword,
not for letting you fall in love.
This is called "Soul-Devouring Spell".
I planted it in your body.
As long as you have any affection for Liu Shao,
the spell will get stimulated,
and break out from your heart and mouth.
If you don't draw back from loving Liu Shao,
the spell will run through your body along with your vitality,
making your blood vessels burst apart
and bringing you the intolerable pain.
When the spell returns back to your palms,
you absolutely will die.
You'd better do yourself a favor!
I don't need a useless disciple.
What is Lu Li doing?
Why isn't he here yet?
[Pearl Pavilion]
Lu Li, what were you doing?
What took you so long?
I was thinking about
getting the King Herb as soon as possible.
Then one day, if I leave,
you can have a foothold in Marquis Wuyang's Mansion when being alone.
What?
You're leaving?
Don't worry.
I'm not leaving.
You...
You
took my money.
If you leave, you have to compensate me.
Ten times the price.
No, 100 times.
I can't afford to it.
Then you're not allowed to leave.
[Pearl Pavilion]
Why did you threaten me to leave?
Is your master sick again
and short of money?
No.
You brought little fish demon here?
Damn fish demon!
Come out!
Liu Shao!
The servant
of the Demon King.
Do you know
where your lord
put the King Herb?
Don't stand there.
I'm just a servant.
I don't know what My Lord did.
Don't give him a hard time.
Get to work.
Let's go.
Hey!
Why? Why?
Why
should I take so much,
while he's taking nothing?
Are you done?
Yes.
Get back to work.
Leave the basin.
Although this place is old,
it's with archaic beauty.
You little demon,
can you stop flirting?
Go clean up.
Over there.
See? It's dirty over there.
Clean it up.
Hurry.
Is he capable of that?
He's just a fish,
not the Demon King.
Even Miss Liu can manage it.
How can Miss Liu's demon be incapable of it?
What do you think?
Mr. Lu is right.
Don't bully honest people.
Me?
Who is the honest one?
Don't bully my demon.
Stop looking!
I'll beat you.
Get back to work.
Damn fish demon!
Fish Demon, you did it on purpose!
You were fooling me!
I didn't mean it.
I'm cleaning.
Come on.
Let me help you put the books in order.
Mr. Lu,
books shouldn't be placed like this.
Demon King in White,
don't think I fear you.
If you don't stop acting recklessly,
Miss Liu Shao will punish you.
Here you go!
Stop fighting!
Stop!
What are you doing?
Are you two trying to rebel?
Look at what you've done.
He started the fight.
The broom started it.
What are you talking about?
Stop arguing. Just think about how to clean it up.
Or I'll make you into sugar-stewed pear juice.
And you.
I'll chop you
into fillets
for stewing pickles.
Unfortunately, I'm not a real pear.
I wonder if this guy in front of us
is a real carp.
I'm sorry.
It was my fault.
Of course it was your fault.
Can't you stop arguing?
Look at these books.
We need to get them sorted out
and put back in order.
Can we make it in a month?
This is...
You cast the spell?
You cast it?
Is this book a demon too?
It can get itself sorted.
I heard
there was an ancient book from the Immortal Palace left in the mortal world.
It's called "Magic Plant Code".
It's a rare magic weapon.
With the Code, any plants in the Three Realms can be cultivated.
Any plants?
Including the King Herb?
That's right.
I know what to do!
[Fairyland in the Code]
It's so lively.
I think
this must be the world in the Code.
I think so.
Little demon.
What do you think
about this?
At least the things here
should be real.
I wonder if there's a herbal medicine shop here.
I hope we can find the King Herb.
We have to find it anyway.
Why don't we wander around and look for it?
Let's go.
I'll try something else.
Try some.
It looks delicious.
How much is this?
"Grasswort picked for half a day can't fill up the basket,
I missed my husband so much and left the basket on the road."
["Grasswort picked for half a day can't fill up the basket, I missed my husband so much and left the basket on the road."]
Let me tell you.
Such vendors who can read poems
will surely ask for a high price.
Let me deal with it.
You illiteratus.
You're unlearned.
How dare you insult me
with money!
You are not welcomed here.
Leave here, Miss.
Just leave.
-This isn't money. -Leave here.
-It's a golden leaf. -You're not welcomed here.
I don't want you to be my customer.
It's golden.
Enough.
-Ignorant girl. -Let's go.
What does he mean?
He thinks we are illiterate.
-What? -Let's go.
Stop it.
Here you are.
Cotton candy!
How much is this?
It's free.
Everything here is free.
Free?
This world in the Code respect talent and knowledge most.
["Let's pick plantains, let's get plantains."]
As long as you can tell the ingredients indicated by the poems,
you'll get what are sold.
"Grasswort picked for half a day can't fill up the basket,
I missed my husband so much and left the basket on the road."
Grasswort,
the sprout of the Xanthium,
can cure cold and headache.
Impressive!
Such a talent. If you want anything,
just take it.
Have a taste.
It's delicious.
I won't let you win...
It's just to recognize plants.
What's so hard about it?
"Let's pick plantains,
let's get plantains."
This is it.
Here you are.
["Grasswort picked for half a day can't fill up the basket, I missed my husband so much and left the basket on the road."]
That's easy.
Mr. Lu is indeed knowledgeable.
You even know this herb!
Grass named "Carefree".
It's Carefree Grass.
I can't lose to him.
["Let's pick plantains, let's get plantains."]
"Zhaoyan" [flower],
it blooms at dawn and withers at dusk.
Let's go.
["I climbed up the hill and collected fritillaries to drive away my sadness; women are sentimental but also have their principles."]
Chickweed.
Indigofera.
Xu Changqing!
This old demon...
He's so proud of his living a few hundred years longer than me
and reading a few more books than me.
Shameless!
If you're angry about it,
then read more books.
This place is really special.
Neither money nor martial arts are pursued.
Only knowledge is highly valued.
People here must be interesting.
Even you don't know it?
Here you are.
The character "蝱" in the poem
refers to the fritillary grass, right?
Yes.
This plant name is rarely-seen.
How did you come to know it?
My master has a cough.
He always eats this.
There's really someone able to pass the test of the spirit fire.
The one who obtained the spirit fire
is the female disciple of our sect, Liu Shao.
The one who brought the spirit fire out
was another disciple, Lu Li.
Liu Shao, Lu Li?
Yes.
Unfortunately,
they haven't
brought back the King Herb yet.
The demons are rampant in the Three Realms now.
I lost eighty percent of my power
because of saving Lu Li.
If a powerful demon attacks,
I'm afraid I won't be able to repel the enemy.
Immortal Master,
the spiritual power of Liu Shao is abnormal.
I'm wondering
if we can use her power
to eliminate the demons in the mortal world.
Don't act rashly.
The decision should be made after it's discussed in the Immortal Palace.
Now, I can help you absorb the power of the spirit fire
to restore some of your vitality.
It can help with the emergency for the time being.
Then you can go find the King Herb.
When the mortal world is in trouble,
the Immortal Palace won't stand by and do nothing.
Thank you, Immortal Master.
Good.
Good!
-So beautiful. -Nice.
Again.
"The reeds are pale; the dew becomes frost".
[To create wonders with a brush.]
The person I love is on the other side of the water.
I know the answer.
It should be reeds!
You are so brilliant, Miss.
In that case,
how about I draw a picture for you
as a souvenir?
We don't want pictures.
We're here for the King Herb.
Do you know it?
I don't know.
Since you passed my test,
I should draw a picture for you.
Look, it's a beautiful day
with beauties and talents here.
[To create wonders with a brush, Painting of Golden Autumn]
It's a pity if you give up the chance.
What you draw are plants, insects and birds.
There's no portrait.
Are you
capable of portrait painting?
Of course.
Let me show you.
A woman in Marquis Wuyang's robe can also look so good!
[To create wonders with a brush]
Yes.
Keep this posture.
Don't move.
Smile like me.
Blow it.
The squatting friend!
To pick up the flower like an immortal.
To pick up the flower!
To pick up!
Do you know how an immortal picks up the flower?
Get down! Get down!
Your eyes
should be sharper.
How about you be more witty?
It's better to be sharp.
Yes.
The one in white.
Can you play the flute?
Play the flute?
It's done.
Such a lifelike picture,
isn't it?
Wait, this is different
from what you showed us.
Of course.
Why would he draw the portrait of Marquis Wuyang?
This painting must be very important.
Sir.
I think you're lying.
Can you tell the truth?
Well...
What truth?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Liu Shao.
You say it.
I?
There are
many vendors here.
But none of them accept real goods.
It's free.
Everything here is free.
Only you
ask for no test of plant names.
["Let's pick plantains, let's get plantains."]
["I climbed up the hill and collected fritillaries to drive away my sadness; women are sentimental but also have their principles."]
The questions of other vendors are difficult.
But your questions are the simplest.
"The reeds are pale; the dew becomes frost".
It means you deliberately let us find you.
Since you passed my test,
I should draw a picture for you.
The woman in the portrait
was wearing Marquis Wuyang's armor.
[To create wonders with a brush, Painting of Golden Autumn]
But you are only good at drawing flowers, insects and birds.
So,
how did you get this painting?
This only shows
you're different from the others in this fairyland.
That's right.
Otherwise,
maybe you are the master here.
Are you the master of the "Magic Plant Code"?
Then you must know where the King Herb is.
So what?
The "Magic Plant Code" is filled with plants.
They are all my descendants.
This is my world.
So what we see
are all grass demons.
They all grew up in the book.
No wonder they are so fond of literature.
That's right!
I'll make it clear today.
You can't get out.
Give it to me.
What are you doing?
Weren't you arrogant just now?
Let me make it clear today.
This painting is for our freedom.
Is this painting that important?
Why didn't I know?
It doesn't matter.
Little demon, come here.
Burn this painting.
Okay.
So you're from the Aquatic Demon clan.
How dare you fool me?
It's not fun at all.
Fine, I'll send you out.
We're finally back.
I'll teach you a lesson.
Damn fish demon.
You reacted quickly just now.
Were you really going to make a fire ball
and burn that painting?
How should the Aquatic Family set fire?
Please teach me, Mr. Lu.
Anyway,
you did well today.
Go out.
Turn left.
There's a big water tank.
See it as a reward for your action.
You really care about me, don't you?
Are you in need of water?
You... You're dry now.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Where is that "painter" we met just now?
Where did he go?
Sorry.
I showed up hastily just now.
Let me formally introduce myself.
My name's "Wansui" [long live]!
I'm Father of all plants.
All plants in the mortal world
are my disciples.
However, time has not made me more arrogant,
but endowed me with modesty.
[Pearl Pavilion]
You were so proud in there
just now , weren't you?
I won't tell you any information about the King Herb.
You're quite stubborn.
Forget it.
Let's go.
I'm the ancestor.
How could I not know?
Will you
come back?
No.
Why?
Isn't it fun here?
Without us being with you,
old grass,
you feel lonely now?
You feel the sense of emptiness?
I have the "Magic Plant Code".
The world there suits my heart the most.
Why would I be lonely?
Then just go have fun with
those boring plants.
Enjoy yourself.
Let's go.
It seems that
you can't get out...
What did you say?
Demon King in White entered Marquis Wuyang's Mansion?
Yes.
That day, I saw
Demon King in White turned into a fish
and was taken into the Mansion by Liu Shao.
Demon King in White.
A demon
entered the place for hunting demons...
What are you doing?
Just with a drop of Liu Shao's blood,
I can then confirm
if she's the person I'm looking for.
[Pearl Pavilion]
Ten thousand years?
You've lived for 10,000 years.
How have you lived so long?
What did you look like when you were young?
Were you in human form at that time?
Listen to it.
Stupid question.
Yes.
Sorry, I was wrong.
I was wrong.
Were you like the ginseng doll
on New Year paintings?
Will each of your hair
become a herb when it's torn out?
If you're planted in spring,
many more of your fellows will come out in autumn, right?
I don't know!
I have no idea!
Why do you have so many questions?
You do have too many questions.
Do I?
No.
Go ahead.
How about
you answer one or two of my questions first?
What do you think?
This girl
is obviously very innocent.
But you are different.
What's wrong with me?
Do you have any secrets?
What secret can I have?
Fine.
I'll give you a chance.
You can ask me.
Who is your father?
I'm an orphan.
My master brought me up.
Who is your master?
You sly old man.
I've answered your question.
Now it's your turn to answer.
Did we
went up into the "Magic Plant Code"?
Yes.
Who is your master?
My master is Lu Sheng.
Lu Sheng?
I heard about him ten thousand years ago.
Is it true?
Now that you mention it,
I remember it...
What?
My master
mentioned you before.
What?
My master mentioned you before.
Yes.
Say it.
Well...
Lu Li...
Lu Li told me,
his master always said
a King Herb turned into a man ten thousand years ago.
He's good-looking,
and kind.
He's very smart,
and is a very...
A very good demon, right?
A very good demon!
He really said so.
I feel flattered.
But it's true that I'm the ancestor
who is adored
among people and plants,
Shouldn't you tell us now
how to get the King Herb
with the "Magic Plant Code"?
You're trying to trick me out of the secret, right?
You have to obey the rules we agreed on.
Actually, it doesn't matter if I tell you.
But
you have to promise me one thing.
What is it?
What?
You come to play with me every day.
If you can make me happy,
I'll tell you how to plant the King Herb.
What do you think?
Play with you?
I know who can do it.
Who?
He.
The gentleman in white?
Yes, he is my demon.